SFU Archives reference and display materials collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Subject Files, [ca 1870] - 2000; F-247-4; 1.24 m of textual records 1305 photographs 91 contact sheets 204 negatives 129 slides 15 sketches
  - Homecoming display, 25th Anniversary; text, publications, Student Radicalization text, 1965 - 1990; F-247-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - A&W Root Bear; 5x7, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Academic Quadrangle Construction; various, [ca 1963]; F-247-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: Leonard Frank Photos.
  - Academic Quadrangle, exterior, 1966 - 1988; F-247-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Administration Building, interior; 8x10, [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: John Fulker, photographer; 1083-15.
  - Admissions Protest, 1968; F-247-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Aerial - SFU; various, color photocopies, [ca 1973] - [ca 1983]; F-247-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Aerial - construction of SFU; various (possibly originals?), [ca 1963] - [ca 1983]; F-247-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: George Allen Aerial Photos Ltd.; AVC.
  - Animals (deer); 2 8x10, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: Peter Hulbert, Province.
  - Archaeology Expeditions; 8x10, 1984; F-247-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Hobler, Philip M.; Lincoln, Neville J.; Cairns, Marilyn; Textual records; Pender Island
  - Architectural Competition: A New University for BC; Universities Act, 1963 - 1964; F-247-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Architectural Drawings / SFU Buildings, [ca 1964]; F-247-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Architecture Competitions; 3 8x10, 1963; F-247-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Architectural Models; 8x10, 1963; F-247-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: Herbert L. McDonald.
  - Architectural Photographs; various sizes, negatives, 1965; F-247-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Art Gallery; 3 8x10, 1971; F-247-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: Audio Visual Centre, 14-10-71, No. 57.
  - Artwork: negative, oil painting, SFU construction, 1965; F-247-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Association of B.C. Archivists: negatives, contact sheet, 1983; F-247-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Association of University and College Employees; 8x10, 5x7, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Athletics memorabilia - old tickets, mini banner, etc., 1975 - 1990; F-247-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
    Creator's original file classification code: Athletics Dept..
  - Awards, Academic: 8x10 - Brad Palmer, 8x10 - Chris Siu, 2-5x7 - David Runnings, 1970 - 1991; F-247-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Awards, Athletic: various, contact sheets, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-24)
  - Bed Race; 2-4x6, 1980; F-247-4-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Blood Donor Clinic; 4-5x5, [197-?]; F-247-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Boilers; 2-8x10, 1973; F-247-4-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Building construction photographs and slides, 1965 - 1992; F-247-4-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: Erickson and Massey, etc..
  - Burnaby aerial photographs, map, photographs, 1904 - 1993; F-247-4-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Burnaby aerial photographs - positives, 1956; F-247-4-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Burnaby's Centennial calendars, 1992; F-247-4-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: City of Burnaby.
  - Burns (Robert) Day - photos, [ca 1965] - [ca 1993]; F-247-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: IMC, M&PR.
  - Burns (Robert) Day - poems and text, [198-]; F-247-4-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: Book of Robert Burns, etc..
  - Bus stop, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Cafeterias, East Concourse, Mall; various sizes, [ca 1969] - [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: Donovan.
  - Campus, [ca 1965]; F-247-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Captain Canada, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: Pete Ogloff.
  - Cards (SFU Season's Greetings cards) - 17, [ca 1985]; F-247-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Cartoons - SFU political; various sizes but mostly 8.5x14, [ca 1963] - [ca 1965]; F-247-4-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: Student Society.
  - Chinese New Year - photographs, red pockets, text, etc., 1993; F-247-4-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Christmas - photograph, 1979; F-247-4-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Christmas cards - layout, card designs, [ca 1985] - [ca 1986]; F-247-4-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Burnaby Image Bank (SFU photos with captions), 1990; F-247-4-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Classes, indoors, [ca 1975] - [ca 1979]; F-247-4-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: Audio Visual Centre, IMC.
  - Classes, outdoors; 8x10, 5x7, [ca 1966] - [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Classroom complex; slides, 1969; F-247-4-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Clubs Day; 5x5, 8x10, [ca 1979]; F-247-4-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Computing services; 5x7, 1971; F-247-4-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Congresses and Convention, 1978; F-247-4-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Construction - Ring Road; various, [ca 1979] - [ca 1981]; F-247-4-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Construction - Halpern and Applied Sciences buildings, [ca 1988] - [ca 1990]; F-247-4-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Ceremonies - Maggie Benston Centre, 1996; F-247-4-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: Ceremonies Office.
  - Construction - West Mall, MBC Student Services; various, [ca 1992] - [ca 1996]; F-247-4-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 247-25)
  - Convocation - First graduates, 1967; F-247-4-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 247-26)
    Creator's original file classification code: Yearbook, page 40.
  - Convocation photographs, 1967 - 1997; F-247-4-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 247-26)
  - Convocation regalia - text, lists, title headings, [198-?]; F-247-4-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 247-26)
  - Convocation display items, text, publications, 1967 - 1997; F-247-4-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 247-26)
  - Dedication ceremonies with George Pedersen; 17-5x7, 7-8x10, 1978 - 1982; F-247-4-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 247-27)
  - Disabled students, [ca 1978]; F-247-4-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 247-27)
  - Naming of library and science buildings; various contact sheets, negatives, 1982; F-247-4-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 247-27)
  - Opening ceremonies; text, 1994; F-247-4-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 247-27)
  - Maggie Benston Centre, 1996; F-247-4-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 247-27)
  - Opening ceremonies - photos, 1965; F-247-4-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 247-27)
    Creator's original file classification code: Pacific Photographic Services.
  - Opening ceremonies - various contact sheets, negatives, 1965; F-247-4-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 247-27)
    Creator's original file classification code: Pacific Photographic Services, John Helcermanas.
  - Instant University photographs, 1965 - 1993; F-247-4-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 247-28)
  - Physical plant and planning - the first decade, 1990; F-247-4-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 247-28)
    Creator's original file classification code: PP&P.
  - Book - Higher Education in B.C. and a Plan for the Future, [ca 1962]; F-247-4-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 247-28)
  - Original - SFU Development Plan, 1963; F-247-4-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 247-28)
  - Dancers, [ca 1977]; F-247-4-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Day Care Centres - children, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Demonstrations, [ca 1967] - [ca 1978]; F-247-4-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Development of SFU origins and various anniversary signs, [ca 1985]; F-247-4-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Dogs, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Elections, [ca 1972] - [ca 1978]; F-247-4-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Electronics Shop, 1966; F-247-4-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Engineering Faculty, [ca 1980] - [ca 1983]; F-247-4-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
    Creator's original file classification code: Engineering.
  - Facilities Management, 1974; F-247-4-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Field Trips - Squamish Trip, [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Flag - SFU, [ca 1965]; F-247-4-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Forums, Discussion, and Debate, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - French Ambassador's Visit, 1964; F-247-4-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Glass Blowing and Working, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Groundstar Conspiracy, [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Gymnasium / Proposed Sports Centre / Swimming Pool, [ca 1967]; F-247-4-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
    Creator's original file classification code: Ford, Rolly, unknown.
  - Health Services, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Hindmarch's Room, 1981; F-247-4-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
    Creator's original file classification code: UNS 81-1-15.
  - Hitch Hiking Stand; photocopy, [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Hollywood Stars; Xaviera Hollander, Jimmy Stewart, [ca 1973]; F-247-4-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
  - Hong Kong (SFU Dinner 1992) photographs, text, publications, F-247-4-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
    Creator's original file classification code: IMC, Archives.
  - Art Hupy photos of AQ scenes, 1967; F-247-4-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 247-29)
    Creator's original file classification code: 67148-6, -14, -21 [M&PR].
  - Jinan University Exchange, 1981; F-247-4-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Jogging, [ca 1975] - [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Kamloops - Aerial, [197-?]; F-247-4-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Kinesiology, 1982; F-247-4-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Kowallek, Helen (sketches), 1989; F-247-4-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Laboratories; various, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Language Labs, [196-]; F-247-4-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Madge Hogarth House, 1988 - 1990; F-247-4-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Mall / with students, with fountain; various, [198-?]; F-247-4-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: Peak, Audio Visual Centre.
  - Louis Riel House, 1970; F-247-4-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Microphotography - Equipment and Supplies, [ca 1965]; F-247-4-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: Edward Pryor.
  - Mime, 1971; F-247-4-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Musicians, [ca 1966] - [ca 1976]; F-247-4-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Olympics, 1968; F-247-4-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Open House, 1973 - 1978; F-247-4-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: Peak; M&PR.
  - Parachuting, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: Marilyn McFadeyn.
  - SFU Horizons - 1980 Open House; publication, F-247-4-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Parking, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Peak, [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Post Cards (of SFU), 1975 - 1985; F-247-4-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Pipe Band (SFU), [ca 1967] - [ca 1989]; F-247-4-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Pipe Band (SFU), [ca 1965] - [ca 1999]; F-247-4-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR, LIDC, Archives.
  - Physics Summer Research Scholarships (posters), 1973 - 1975; F-247-4-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: Physics Department.
  - Plaques / Medals, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Plaque (of Simon Fraser and Gordon Shrum), 2000; F-247-4-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: Archives, LIDC.
  - Pollution Patrol, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - President's Residence (construction), 1966; F-247-4-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - PSA Strike (photos that accompanied story by Bruce Mason in Peak), 1968; F-247-4-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
  - Pub - opening; article regarding 25 years, 1998; F-247-4-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: IMC; SF News Jan. 8, 1998.
  - Purcell String Quartet, [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 247-30)
    Creator's original file classification code: John Mahler.
  - Radio Stations, [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Registrar's office (photocopy, see Academic Quadrangle, exterior), 1965; F-247-4-0-0-121 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
    Creator's original file classification code: John Helcermanas.
  - Registration, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-122 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Research Vessels; various, [ca 1970] - [ca 1972]; F-247-4-0-0-123 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Rotunda, [ca 1968]; F-247-4-0-0-124 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
    Creator's original file classification code: John Fulker.
  - Rowing, 1964; F-247-4-0-0-125 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
    Creator's original file classification code: Ken Orr.
  - Senate, 1967; F-247-4-0-0-126 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Senior Citizen Program, 1976; F-247-4-0-0-127 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Shrum Science Centre, 1964; F-247-4-0-0-128 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
    Creator's original file classification code: Rhone & Iredale Architects.
  - Shell Station, 1967; F-247-4-0-0-129 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
    Creator's original file classification code: Williams Brothers Photographers.
  - Shell House - construction, 1967; F-247-4-0-0-130 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Shrum, Gordon M.; various, [ca 1870] - 1983; F-247-4-0-0-131 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Shrum, Gordon M.; text, [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-132 (Archival box - standard 247-31)
  - Snow and Ice, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-133 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Staff, Archives, [ca 1970] - [ca 1987]; F-247-4-0-0-134 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
    Creator's original file classification code: Peak, Archives.
  - Staff, Athletics, 1970 - 1980; F-247-4-0-0-135 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Staff, Peak Publications, [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-136 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Staff, SFU Theatre, [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-137 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Staff, University Centre Building, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-138 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Strikes, [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-139 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Student Society Forums, [197-]; F-247-4-0-0-140 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Student Society photographs of posters, 1991; F-247-4-0-0-141 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Student Society representatives (presidents), [ca 1965] - [ca 1973]; F-247-4-0-0-142 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Students, [ca 1966] - [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-143 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
    Creator's original file classification code: LIDC?, Peak.
  - Telephone directory covers (of SFU), [198-]; F-247-4-0-0-144 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
    Creator's original file classification code: Ancillary Services.
  - Television Production (negatives), [197-?]; F-247-4-0-0-145 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Theatre - SFU, 1965 - 1980; F-247-4-0-0-146 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Tour Guides, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-147 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Traffic and Security, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-148 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
    Creator's original file classification code: Donovan, Peak.
  - Transportation Centre, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-149 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
    Creator's original file classification code: Rolly Ford.
  - Trees, [ca 1970] - [ca 1980]; F-247-4-0-0-150 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
    Creator's original file classification code: Carol Goron.
  - Tug of War, [ca 1977]; F-247-4-0-0-151 (Archival box - standard 247-32)
  - Unidentified individuals - Athletics (contact sheets), [ca 1965] - [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-152 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - Unidentified individuals - Athletics portraits, [ca 1965] - [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-153 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - United Way Campaign, 1980; F-247-4-0-0-154 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - University Review Committee, [ca 1978]; F-247-4-0-0-155 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - University Centre Building, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-156 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - Valentine's Day - poems, 1990; F-247-4-0-0-157 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
    Creator's original file classification code: Archives, E. Browning.
  - W.A.C. Bennett Library (exterior), [ca 1965] - [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-158 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - W.A.C. Bennett Library (interior), [ca 1965] - [ca 1970]; F-247-4-0-0-159 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - Western Canadian Universities Marine Biological Station, 1969 - 1973; F-247-4-0-0-160 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - Women's Group Rape Defense Seminar, [ca 1975]; F-247-4-0-0-161 (Archival box - standard 247-33)
  - BC Women's History, Women's History Month, 1995; F-247-4-0-0-162 (Archival box - standard 247-33)